export const katakanaArray = [
  { front: "ア", back: "a" },
  { front: "イ", back: "i" },
  { front: "ウ", back: "u" },
  { front: "エ", back: "e" },
  { front: "オ", back: "o" },
  { front: "カ", back: "ka" },
  { front: "キ", back: "ki" },
  { front: "ク", back: "ku" },
  { front: "ケ", back: "ke" },
  { front: "コ", back: "ko" },
  { front: "サ", back: "sa" },
  { front: "シ", back: "shi" },
  { front: "ス", back: "su" },
  { front: "セ", back: "se" },
  { front: "ソ", back: "so" },
  { front: "タ", back: "ta" },
  { front: "チ", back: "chi" },
  { front: "ツ", back: "tsu" },
  { front: "テ", back: "te" },
  { front: "ト", back: "to" },
  { front: "ナ", back: "na" },
  { front: "ニ", back: "ni" },
  { front: "ヌ", back: "nu" },
  { front: "ネ", back: "ne" },
  { front: "ノ", back: "no" },
  { front: "ハ", back: "ha" },
  { front: "ヒ", back: "hi" },
  { front: "フ", back: "fu" },
  { front: "ヘ", back: "he" },
  { front: "ホ", back: "ho" },
  { front: "マ", back: "ma" },
  { front: "ミ", back: "mi" },
  { front: "ム", back: "mu" },
  { front: "メ", back: "me" },
  { front: "モ", back: "mo" },
  { front: "ヤ", back: "ya" },
  { front: "ユ", back: "yu" },
  { front: "ヨ", back: "yo" },
  { front: "ラ", back: "ra" },
  { front: "リ", back: "ri" },
  { front: "ル", back: "ru" },
  { front: "レ", back: "re" },
  { front: "ロ", back: "ro" },
  { front: "ワ", back: "wa" },
  { front: "ヲ", back: "wo" },
  { front: "ン", back: "n" },
  { front: "ガ", back: "ga" },
  { front: "ギ", back: "gi" },
  { front: "グ", back: "gu" },
  { front: "ゲ", back: "ge" },
  { front: "ゴ", back: "go" },
  { front: "ザ", back: "za" },
  { front: "ジ", back: "ji" },
  { front: "ズ", back: "zu" },
  { front: "ゼ", back: "ze" },
  { front: "ゾ", back: "zo" },
  { front: "ダ", back: "da" },
  { front: "ヂ", back: "ji" },
  { front: "ヅ", back: "zu" },
  { front: "デ", back: "de" },
  { front: "ド", back: "do" },
  { front: "バ", back: "ba" },
  { front: "ビ", back: "bi" },
  { front: "ブ", back: "bu" },
  { front: "ベ", back: "be" },
  { front: "ボ", back: "bo" },
  { front: "パ", back: "pa" },
  { front: "ピ", back: "pi" },
  { front: "プ", back: "pu" },
  { front: "ペ", back: "pe" },
  { front: "ポ", back: "po" },
];
export const hiraganaArray = [
  { front: "あ", frontKatakana: "ア", back: "a" },
  { front: "い", frontKatakana: "イ", back: "i" },
  { front: "う", frontKatakana: "ウ", back: "u" },
  { front: "え", frontKatakana: "エ", back: "e" },
  { front: "お", frontKatakana: "オ", back: "o" },
  { front: "か", frontKatakana: "カ", back: "ka" },
  { front: "き", frontKatakana: "キ", back: "ki" },
  { front: "く", frontKatakana: "ク", back: "ku" },
  { front: "け", frontKatakana: "ケ", back: "ke" },
  { front: "こ", frontKatakana: "コ", back: "ko" },
  { front: "さ", frontKatakana: "サ", back: "sa" },
  { front: "し", frontKatakana: "シ", back: "shi" },
  { front: "す", frontKatakana: "ス", back: "su" },
  { front: "せ", frontKatakana: "セ", back: "se" },
  { front: "そ", frontKatakana: "ソ", back: "so" },
  { front: "た", frontKatakana: "タ", back: "ta" },
  { front: "ち", frontKatakana: "チ", back: "chi" },
  { front: "つ", frontKatakana: "ツ", back: "tsu" },
  { front: "て", frontKatakana: "テ", back: "te" },
  { front: "と", frontKatakana: "ト", back: "to" },
  { front: "な", frontKatakana: "ナ", back: "na" },
  { front: "に", frontKatakana: "ニ", back: "ni" },
  { front: "ぬ", frontKatakana: "ヌ", back: "nu" },
  { front: "ね", frontKatakana: "ネ", back: "ne" },
  { front: "の", frontKatakana: "ノ", back: "no" },
  { front: "は", frontKatakana: "ハ", back: "ha" },
  { front: "ひ", frontKatakana: "ヒ", back: "hi" },
  { front: "ふ", frontKatakana: "フ", back: "fu" },
  { front: "へ", frontKatakana: "ヘ", back: "he" },
  { front: "ほ", frontKatakana: "ホ", back: "ho" },
  { front: "ま", frontKatakana: "マ", back: "ma" },
  { front: "み", frontKatakana: "ミ", back: "mi" },
  { front: "む", frontKatakana: "ム", back: "mu" },
  { front: "め", frontKatakana: "メ", back: "me" },
  { front: "も", frontKatakana: "モ", back: "mo" },
  { front: "や", frontKatakana: "ヤ", back: "ya" },
  { front: "ゆ", frontKatakana: "ユ", back: "yu" },
  { front: "よ", frontKatakana: "ヨ", back: "yo" },
  { front: "ら", frontKatakana: "ラ", back: "ra" },
  { front: "り", frontKatakana: "リ", back: "ri" },
  { front: "る", frontKatakana: "ル", back: "ru" },
  { front: "れ", frontKatakana: "レ", back: "re" },
  { front: "ろ", frontKatakana: "ロ", back: "ro" },
  { front: "わ", frontKatakana: "ワ", back: "wa" },
  { front: "を", frontKatakana: "ヲ", back: "wo" },
  { front: "ん", frontKatakana: "ン", back: "n" },
];
